Ali Muradov

CONTACT

E-mail: amuradov239@gmail.com

Phone: +359889606113

SUMMARY

Self-motivated junior web developer with 1 year of experience and a strong team spirit, a hard worker and studier, with a deep interest in front-end technologies. Good at managing time in a work environment and finishing tasks on time, whatever it takes, including when working under pressure.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Optimal Industries

Oct 2022 - Oct 2023

Junior Web Developer

Developed different kinds of outsourced projects for a variety of companies.

Robert Bosch GmbH

Mar 2023 - Oct 2023

Web Developer

Vacation Tracking System (Implementation and Maintenance):

A PTO and sick days tracking system with review/approval management functionalities. It allows Users to track their remaining leave days. The system allows enhanced reporting functionalities over a given period, departments and employees.

Responsibilities within the project:

- Front-end development and refactoring
- Back-end optimization and refactoring
- Participate in client demo's
- Refactoring legacy code and introducing modern conventions and libraries,

Dates: 03.2023 - now

Team size: 7

Position: Software Engineer

Technologies involved: Node Js, Express Js, Redis, Socket IO, React Js, Typescript,

MySQL, Sequelize

IKEA

Oct 2022 - Mar 2023

Web Developer

OMS (Order Management System):

Web-based logistics software for management and monitoring of warehouse processes and customer orders. Solution Includes a mobile app, web-based back-office system, SMS notification system and kiosk app for managing order queues in stores.

Responsibilities within the project:

- Development of the back-office system
- Implementation of reusable components
- Implementation of app authentication and authorization

App testing,

Dates: 10.2022 - 03.2023

Team size: 8

Ali Muradov

Position: Software Engineer

Technologies involved: .NET, ASP.NET Core, PostgreSQL, EF Core, ReactJS,

Typescript, Keycloak, Gitlab CI/CD, Jenkins, Bash, Docker, LXD

QUALIFICATIONS

- React.js
- JavaScript
- TypeScript
- Material Ui
- Redux
- BitBucket
- MySQL
- Git
- Gitlab
- MsSQL
- Node.js
- Express.js
- AntDesign
- Cucumber
- Agile, Scrum, Waterfall
- Linux, Windows
- Debugging

EDUCATION

Bachelor's in Software Engineering

Sept 2020 - May 2024

PU 'Paisii Hilendarski'

Currently doing my final year for my bachelor's in Software Engineering. Gained a lot of experience in different technologies such as C#, Java, HTML and different RDBMS, such as MSSQL, MySQL, H2 etc.

High School Diploma

Sept 2015 - May 2020

PG 'Gen.Vladimir Zaimov'

Finished a High School with a diploma in Software Engineering with high grades. Mainly studied C# app development.

First English Certificate (FCE)

Sept 2019 - May 2020

C1

Finished a course that allowed me to score an A on the FCE exam.

INTERESTS

Hobbies: Hiking, spending time with friends, gaming, reading self-improvement books.

ADDITIONAL CONTACTS

You can contact me via a direct message on the following social media:

- LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/in/ali-muradov-285891218/
- Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/whitebear1337

Ali Muradov 2